Lish mss., 1951-2017 LMC 2404
Lilly Library
- II. Writings
  - By Other Authors
    - Garrison (end) - Gilbert (Box 51)
      - Gilbert, Jack, (4 folders) (Box 51)
        - [Untitled Collection of Poems] (Box 51)
          - How to Love the Dead (Box 51)
          - I Imagine the Gods (Box 51)
          - In Umbria (Box 51)
          - Infidelity (Box 51)
          - Leporello on Don Giovanni (Box 51)
          - Me and Capablanca (Box 51)
        - The Great Fires Jacket copy (Box 51)
    - Gilbert (end) - Grimson (Box 52)
      - Gilbert, Jack (end), (13 folders) (Box 52)
        - Measuring the Tyger Draft 4 (Box 52)
        - Monolithos Draft 1 (Box 52)
        - Monolithos Draft 2 (Box 52)
        - Monolithos Foul Draft (Box 52)
        - Monolithos Setting ms. (Box 52)
        - Monolithos Final Setting ms. (Box 52)
        - Monolithos Galleys (Box 52)
        - Monolithos Master Galleys (Box 52)
        - Monolithos Master Pages (Box 52)
      - Gill, Brendan (Box 52)
        - Valor (Box 52)
      - Gilmartin, Steven (Box 52)
        - In a Queer Light [aka The Gift (Box 52)
      - Glaze, Eleanor (Box 52)
        - The Distance Between Bed and Earth [aka Distances Between Bed and Earth] (Box 52)
      - Glynn, Thomas (Box 52)
        - Thomas Glynn to Q [aka He Wants to Be Famous Indoors] (Box 52)
      - Goad, Frank A. and Loomis, Edward (Box 52)
        - Acne (Box 52)
      - Goddin, Nell (Box 52)
        - The Holes of the Sapsucker [aka Talk] (Box 52)
      - Goding, Cecile Hanna (Box 52)
        - The Arlington Street Station (Box 52)
        - August 8, 1988 (Box 52)
        - The [Busy?] Dog (Box 52)
        - Erection Stress (Box 52)
        - A Guide for Living (Box 52)
        - Mr. and Mrs. From Missouri [aka Swing Shift] (Box 52)
      - Godwin, Gail (Box 52)
        - The Good Wife [aka Outposts] (Box 52)
        - Notes for a Story [aka Childhood Friends] (Box 52)
        - What She Wore (Box 52)
      - Goff, Cindy (Box 52)
        - God [aka God Is a Vampire] (Box 52)
        - Heritage (Box 52)
        - Northside (Box 52)
      - Gold, Herbert (Box 52)
        - Breeding the Wild Mosquito (Box 52)
        - A Death on the East Side (Box 52)
        - In the Community of Girls and the Commerce of Culture (Manhattan 1955-1960) (Box 52)
        - A Very Personal Colleague of Andy Warhol (Box 52)
      - Goldberg, Judith (Box 52)
        - Catching Ben, or Hope, Color, and the State of Maine (Box 52)
        - An Element Called Surprise (Box 52)
        - Millard Fillmore! Martin van Buren! (Box 52)
        - Nam, Nam, Nam (Box 52)
        - Needing Nurses in Other Rooms (Box 52)
        - Salvation (Box 52)
      - Goodwin, Stephen (Box 52)
        - His Heart (Box 52)
      - Goolrick, Robert Cooke (Box 52)
        - Six Days, Five Delicious Nighs in Sunwashed Symbia (Box 52)
      - Gosnell, Stephen (Box 52)
        - Show Me Something in a Soft, Quiet War Toy (Box 52)
        - Twilight of the Profs (Box 52)
        - [Have you a vision of your children…] (Box 52)
        - [We'll go on the assumption that you want…] (Box 52)
      - Gould, Scott (Box 52)
        - Hitler [aka Territories] (Box 52)
      - Gram, Richard (Box 52)
        - Place We are, Place We Leave (Box 52)
      - Graves, John (Box 52)
        - Hardscrable (Box 52)
      - Greenberg, Mark (Box 52)
        - Mark Greenberg to Q [aka With Love], (3 folders) (Box 52)
      - Greenberg, Pamela, (3 folders) (Box 52)
        - Banquet (Box 52)
        - Flood (Box 52)
        - Lagunitas, 1978 (Box 52)
        - Love Poem #206 (Box 52)
        - Ode (Box 52)
        - Prarie (Box 52)
        - Where Once It Stood (Box 52)
      - Gremmel, William (Box 52)
        - The Little Family (Box 52)
      - Griffin, Michael (Box 52)
        - It's a Sin to Tell a Lie (Box 52)
      - Griffith, Kevin (Box 52)
        - The Boy in the Well (Box 52)
        - Emily Dickinson (Box 52)
        - The Kwik-Stop of the Damned (Box 52)
        - Poem Without a Photo (Box 52)
        - Some Days, You Are That Man (Box 52)
        - Net (Box 52)
        - Summary of Charges (Box 52)
        - The Retreat into Day (Box 52)
      - Grimmett, Neil (Box 52)
        - Cider (Box 52)
        - The Hornets [aka Carried Away by Angels] (Box 52)
      - Grimson, Todd (Box 52)
        - Fried Chicken (Box 52)
        - The Revolution [aka Ritual of the Dead] (Box 52)
    - Grinstead - Hannah (start) (Box 53)
      - Grinstead, David (Box 53)
        - Kills (Box 53)
      - Grossbach, Robert (Box 53)
        - The Ground of the Night Air (Box 53)
      - Guista, Michael (Box 53)
        - Still Life (Box 53)
      - Gullino, Derek (Box 53)
        - Celeste (Box 53)
        - Dancing for Men (Box 53)
        - Disease (Box 53)
        - Falepopo's Cadillac (Box 53)
        - Gadamer's Maid (Box 53)
        - Hungarian Woman (Box 53)
        - Journey's by Sea (Box 53)
        - Men without Women (Box 53)
        - The Outlaw Mother-in-Law (Box 53)
        - Pops (Box 53)
        - Twain (Box 53)
        - Where Our Linen Comes From (Box 53)
      - Gunzenhauser, Lynn C. (Box 53)
        - Father Portrait (Box 53)
      - Gusewelle, C.W. (Box 53)
        - August 20-26 (Box 53)
      - Gutierrez, Stephen D. (Box 53)
        - Walter's Sorrow (Box 53)
      - Haas, Charles (Box 53)
        - A Western (Box 53)
      - Halberstadt, John (Box 53)
        - Air [aka The Oxtgen Tanks] (Box 53)
        - Selections from I'm in Love with Joanne Talsma (Box 53)
      - Haley, Albert (Box 53)
        - Down on the Farm (Box 53)
        - Moon Shot (Box 53)
        - Snow Eagles (Box 53)
        - Tag: A Grocery Story (Box 53)
        - That Oklahoma Flash (Box 53)
      - Halliday, Ray (Box 53)
        - Bowling in Jersey [aka The Great3es Bowler in New Jersey (Box 53)
        - Dance, Mice, Dance (Box 53)
        - Farted (Box 53)
        - Fourth (Box 53)
        - The Happiest Guy on the Train (Box 53)
        - The Inquiry [aka Like a Dog] (Box 53)
        - New Baltimore Service Area (Box 53)
        - New Format (Box 53)
        - Right Out of a Machine [aka Homeless Woman with Bag Outside the Bank Machine (Box 53)
        - Wax Paper (Box 53)
      - Hamann, Shannon (Box 53)
        - The Wind (Box 53)
      - Hannah, Barry (Box 53)
        - Stories, (4 folders) (Box 53)
          - The Catalogue [aka The Cantata in the Catlogue] (Box 53)
          - Christ Striding (Box 53)
          - Coming Close to Donna (Box 53)
          - The Ground of the Night Air (Box 53)
          - Deaf and Dumb [aka The Courage of Minny Temple] (Box 53)
          - Death of a Bitch (Box 53)
          - Evening of the Yarp: A Report by Roonswent Dover (Box 53)
          - Escape to Newark [aka Do It Yourself] (Box 53)
          - Getting It (including Minny Gets It Regular and Green Gets It At Last) (Box 53)
          - Green Gets It (Box 53)
          - Hey Jack (Box 53)
          - How Good Was It? (Box 53)
          - Love too Long (Box 53)
          - Man in the Street (Box 53)
          - Midnight and I'm Not Famous Yet (Box 53)
          - Mother Rooney Unscrolls the Hurt: A Tiny Novel (Box 53)
          - Quadberry (Box 53)
          - Return to Return (Box 53)
          - Sources Agree Rock Swoon Has No Past (Box 53)
          - Southern [aka End and All in Richmond; When He Burned His House) (Box 53)
          - That's True [aka Not at the Very Last a Coward] (Box 53)
          - Tuscaloose, Where I Live (Box 53)
        - Airships Pages, (2 folders) (Box 53)
        - Airships Misc. Pages (Box 53)
        - Airships Galleys, (2 folders) (Box 53)
        - Airships Retouched Galleys, (4 of 5 folders) (Box 53)
    - Hannah (cont.) (Box 54)
      - Hannah, Barry (cont.) (Box 54)
        - Airships Retouched Galleys, (last of 5 folders) (Box 54)
        - Airships Blues (Box 54)
        - Behold the Man Transfigured in his Husbanding: Three Stories (Box 54)
          - Home Free [aka With All the Old Trembling Men] (Box 54)
          - At Home [aka One Place for Another] (Box 54)
          - Homeless [aka Testimony of Gardens] (Box 54)
        - Captain Maximus Stories (Box 54)
          Note: see 24 Aug 1984 correspondence
          - Watch Out, It's a Big One (Box 54)
          - Hey Joe (Box 54)
          - Nothing Else to Do (Box 54)
        - Captain Maximus Stories - Photocopies (Box 54)
          - American Sportsman [aka Watch Out, It's a Big One ] (Box 54)
          - Idaho [aka Hey Joe (Box 54)
          - I Am Shaking to Death [aka Nothing Else to Do] (Box 54)
          - Football Heroes (Box 54)
          - Even Greenland [aka John, This Plane's on Fire ] (Box 54)
          - Ride, Fly, Penetrate, Loiter (Box 54)
          - It Spoke of Exactly the Things [Black Butterfly] (Box 54)
        - Captain Maximus Galleys (Box 54)
        - Captain Maximus Master Set (Box 54)
        - Maximum Ned (Box 54)
        - Ray Draft 1 (Box 54)
        - Ray Draft 2 (Box 54)
        - Ray Draft 3 (Box 54)
        - Ray Printer's ms. (Box 54)
        - Ray Galleys (Box 54)
        - Ray Master Proofs, (2 folders) (Box 54)
        - Ray Repros Proofs (Box 54)
        - Ray Blues (Box 54)
    - Hannah (end) - Hempel (Box 55)
      - Hannah, Barry (end) (Box 55)
        - The Tennis Handsome Copy 1, (2 folders) (Box 55)
        - The Tennis Handsome Copy 2, (2 folders) (Box 55)
      - Hanson, Michele (Box 55)
        - How Bawble Made Them All Happy (Box 55)
        - Table Manners (Box 55)
      - Hardy, Edward (Box 55)
        - Jerry [aka Bad Pets] (Box 55)
      - Hardy, Melissa (Box 55)
        - How I Was Made an Orphan the Second Time (Box 55)
      - Harker, Steven (Box 55)
        - Orange Delite (Box 55)
      - Harmon, Joshua (Box 55)
        - Signs (Box 55)
      - Harris, Daniel (Box 55)
        - First, Harris (Box 55)
        - Second, Harris (Box 55)
      - Harris, Evan (Box 55)
        - The Hum (Box 55)
        - The Spit (Box 55)
        - Wedding Elements (Box 55)
      - Harris, MacDonald (Box 55)
        - A Memoir from the Lab (Box 55)
      - Harrison, William (Box 55)
        - The Arsons of Desire (Box 55)
        - Down the Blue Hole [aka In America] (Box 55)
        - Roller Ball Murder (Box 55)
      - Hassall, K. (Box 55)
        - Parable (Box 55)
      - Hassler, Jon (Box 55)
        - The Cheerleader [aka The Distant Cheerleader] (Box 55)
      - Hatta, Mari (Box 55)
        - As I Line My Eyes with Black (Box 55)
        - Broken Sestina for a Samurai's Daughter (Box 55)
        - A List for the Hard of Hearing (Box 55)
        - Waitress (Box 55)
      - Hays, Daniel (Box 55)
        - Daniel Hayes to Q (Box 55)
      - Hayward (Box 55)
        - Orange with Reciept (Box 55)
        - Snow (Box 55)
      - Hazuka, Tom (Box 55)
        - Playing Hard to Take (Box 55)
      - Healey, Lynne (Box 55)
        - Renaissance of the Short Story (Box 55)
      - Heberton, Laura (Box 55)
        - Fish (Box 55)
      - Heffernan, Michael (Box 55)
        - Poems (Box 55)
          - Afternoon of the Hun (Box 55)
          - The Boulevardier (Box 55)
          - The Council (Box 55)
          - Stickbug (Box 55)
        - Rendering Aquinas (Box 55)
      - Hemingway, Ernest, (2 folders) (Box 55)
        - Islands in the Stream (Box 55)
        - Excerpts of Writings (Box 55)
      - Hemingway, Mary (Box 55)
        - An American Childhood (Box 55)
      - Hempel, Amy, (8 folders) (Box 55)
        - Stories, (3 folders) (Box 55)
          - The Annex (Box 55)
          - Antarctica (Box 55)
          - At the Gates of the Animal Kingdom (Box 55)
          - Breathing Jesus (Box 55)
          - How Bawble Made Them All Happy (Box 55)
          - The Center [aka Serlait] (Box 55)
          - The Club Bread Vacation (Box 55)
          - Jerry [aka Bad Pets] (Box 55)
          - Daylight Come (Box 55)
          - Du Jour (Box 55)
          - The Game of Empty Hands (Box 55)
          - Going (Box 55)
          - The Harvest [aka Marriageability] (Box 55)
          - In the Cemetary where Al Jolson Is Buried (Box 55)
          - In Situ (Box 55)
          - In a Tub (Box 55)
          - A Letter to Q (Box 55)
          - Live from the Deaf Club (Box 55)
          - Live from the Death Club (Box 55)
          - The Man in Bogota [aka Reason to Live] (Box 55)
          - Maximum Hannah or The Slow Fire of Barry Hannah (Box 55)
          - Murder [aka Boys and Girls] (Box 55)
          - Nashville Gone to Ashes (Box 55)
          - [On the nicer side of a not nice street…] (Box 55)
          - Page after Page (Box 55)
          - Piece Work (Box 55)
          - The Rest of God (Box 55)
          - San Francisco (Box 55)
          - Three Popes Walk into a Bar (Box 55)
          - Today Will Be a Quiet Day (Box 55)
          - Tonight Is a Favor to Holly [aka From the People Who Brought You Fat Chance; West on Highway One] (Box 55)
          - Triste but True (Box 55)
          - Tumble Home (Box 55)
          - [The trees are all on crutches…] (Box 55)
          - Under No Moon (Box 55)
          - When It's Human Instead of When It's a Dog [aka What Would Do It] (Box 55)
          - Why I'm Here [aka Calling] (Box 55)
          - Wittgenstein's Mistress (Box 55)
          - Untitled (Box 55)
        - At the Gates of the Animal Kingdom Author's Galleys (Box 55)
        - At the Gates of the Animal Kingdom Page Proofs (Box 55)
        - Reasons to Live Galleys (Box 55)
        - Reasons to Live Author's Galleys (Box 55)
        - What He Knows So Well (Box 55)
    - Hempstead - Howland (Box 56)
      - Hempstead, Avery, (4 folders) (Box 56)
        - Apricots [aka The Apricot Tree] (Box 56)
        - Arrangments [aka Man with a Missing Earlobe] (Box 56)
        - Babycakes (Box 56)
        - How Bawble Made Them All Happy (Box 56)
        - Book [aka A Change of Seats] (Box 56)
        - Canard (Box 56)
        - Jerry [aka Bad Pets] (Box 56)
        - The Denture [aka Motherlove] (Box 56)
        - The Dispatcher [aka Gable and Lombard and Cary Grant] (Box 56)
        - Dreyfus on Walter (Box 56)
        - An Evening with the Pale People (Box 56)
        - Fine Germs and Low Conversation (Box 56)
        - First Class (Box 56)
        - Flutters (Box 56)
        - Forests of the Night (Box 56)
        - Gilbert and Sullivan (Box 56)
        - Gomco (Box 56)
        - The Hollywood Babies' Club (Box 56)
        - The Hollywood Dream (Box 56)
        - A Little Coffee in the Morning (Box 56)
        - The Man in the Back Seat or Arnie and the Mumu Crowd (Box 56)
        - The Money of Our Family [aka Child of Aliens] (Box 56)
        - The News [aka On the Southern Coast of France] (Box 56)
        - The Other End (Box 56)
        - Retrospective (Box 56)
        - Reverse=Spotted (Box 56)
        - Rockpile (Box 56)
        - Rules (Box 56)
        - Someone Said J.D. Salinger Had Died (Box 56)
        - Sometimes, It's Brian [aka The Man from Cartier ] (Box 56)
        - The Spanish Lesson (Box 56)
        - String (Box 56)
        - To the Monkey House (Box 56)
        - Toothbrush (Box 56)
        - Tye Powers Blues (Box 56)
        - The Woman Called Bambi Goldenspots or Moving Day (Box 56)
        - Woman in the Red Raincoat (Box 56)
      - Henderson, Bill (Box 56)
        - His Son (Box 56)
      - Hendrickson, Robert (Box 56)
        - The Watcher [aka He Is Home] (Box 56)
      - Hennessey, Eileen (Box 56)
        - Eileen Hennessay to Q [After the Ball] (Box 56)
        - Electra at the Well (Box 56)
        - For Oedipus It Was So Bad That He Put Out His Own Eyes (Box 56)
        - Judgment Passed on Electra (Box 56)
        - Morning (Box 56)
        - The Situation (Box 56)
        - World Series (Box 56)
      - Herr, Michael, (4 folders) (Box 56)
        - Jubilee Draft 1 (Box 56)
        - Jubilee Draft 2 (Box 56)
        - Jubilee Draft 3 (Box 56)
        - Viet Memories (Box 56)
      - Hersey, John (Box 56)
      - From The Conspiracy (Box 56)
      - Heuler, Karen (Box 56)
        - In Livingston (Box 56)
      - Hewat, Alan V. (Box 56)
        - Bear, You Know? (Box 56)
        - Men Against the Sea (Box 56)
        - Surfacing (Box 56)
        - [(c) Wives of Professional Athletes…] (Box 56)
      - Hickins, Michael, (2 folders) (Box 56)
      - Stories (Box 56)
        - Afair [aka One Day Affair] (Box 56)
        - The Backswing of the Slugger (Box 56)
        - Ernie the Counselor [aka Post Coitum Animale Tristum Est] (Box 56)
        - In the Borough-Wides [aka Taking It] (Box 56)
        - Summer Romance (Box 56)
        - The Violent Society (Box 56)
        - Bill in Love [aka Circa Someplace in America] (Box 56)
      - Hickman, David (Box 56)
        - Narcissus Diary #31 (Box 56)
      - Hickoff, Stephen (Box 56)
        - Canned Laughter (Box 56)
        - Dor Fucks Jim (Box 56)
        - Hunger, About It (Box 56)
        - The News & World Report (Box 56)
        - Real or Unreal Pancake Syrup (Box 56)
        - Son, Not Even Your Mother… (Box 56)
      - Hirsch, Edward (Box 56)
        - And Who Will Look Upon Our Testimoy (Box 56)
      - Hoar, Jere (Box 56)
        - The Last Feminine Woman in the World (Box 56)
      - Hochberg, Matthew (Box 56)
        - Justice (Box 56)
      - Hochman, Lucy (Box 56)
        - Mollusks (Box 56)
      - Hoda, Shahid (Box 56)
        - The Catch (Box 56)
        - An Empty Poem (Box 56)
        - The Mistake (Box 56)
        - The New Poem (Box 56)
        - October 15 (Box 56)
        - Scenes from a Movie (Box 56)
        - Untitled (Box 56)
        - The Valise (Box 56)
        - The Women's Issue at a Friend's (Box 56)
      - Hodges, John (Box 56)
        - Filet Mignon (Box 56)
      - Hogan, Wayne (Box 56)
      - Assorted Drawings (Box 56)
      - Holland, Noy, (2 folders) (Box 56)
      - Stories (Box 56)
        - Delicious (Box 56)
        - Nothing Like Tuscaloosa [aka The Girl] (Box 56)
        - Someone Is Always Waiting (Box 56)
        - Winter Bodies (Box 56)
        - Her Children, Waiting (Box 56)
      - Holland, Travis (Box 56)
        - Decameron (Box 56)
        - Meat (Box 56)
      - Holmes, Olivia (Box 56)
        - Anna's Promise (Box 56)
      - Holst (Box 56)
        - Another Impostor (Box 56)
        - Chess (Box 56)
        - A Following (Box 56)
        - The Monroe Street Monster (Box 56)
      - Homes, Amy (Box 56)
        - The Dress [aka A Good Day] (Box 56)
      - Hopeloff, Zero (Box 56)
        - Babel (Box 56)
        - Joseph (Box 56)
        - (O) Eddie-piss (Box 56)
      - Hopkins, Diane (Box 56)
        - The Nipple of the Queen (Box 56)
      - Horowitz, Syvlia [aka Sylvia Adele Deutsch] (Box 56)
        - Bananas, Two for a Penny (Box 56)
        - A Crumpled Tissue (Box 56)
      - Howland, Bette, (3 folders) (Box 56)
        - Stories (Box 56)
          - Grisha Lapidus (Box 56)
          - The Landlady (Box 56)
          - The Life They Gave Me [aka The Life You Gave Me] (Box 56)
          - The Old Wheeze (Box 56)
        - Birds of a Feather (Box 56)
        - Things to Come and Go (Box 56)
    - Huddle - Just (Box 57)
      - Huddle, David (Box 57)
        - The Interrogation of the Prisoner Bung by the Sergeart Tree and Mister Hawkins (Box 57)
      - Hudson, Gabriel (Box 57)
        - Litany (Box 57)
        - How Bawble Made Them All Happy (Box 57)
        - The Judge (Box 57)
      - Hulse, Jerry (Box 57)
        - Jerry [aka Bad Pets] (Box 57)
      - Humphrey, William (Box 57)
        - A Texas Dying (Box 57)
      - Hunter, David M. (Box 57)
        - Direction (Box 57)
        - The Weatherman (Box 57)
      - Huntington, Margaret (Box 57)
        - Fire and Ice (Box 57)
      - Hutton, William (Box 57)
        - My Eyes Are Running (Box 57)
        - Plax (Box 57)
        - The Story of Yes and No (Box 57)
      - Ingersoll, Glenn (Box 57)
        - The Artificial Sump Pump (Box 57)
        - The Heart's Work (Box 57)
      - Iossel, Mikhail (Box 57)
        - Wings (Box 57)
      - Irving, John (Box 57)
        - Almost in Iowa (Box 57)
        - Dog in the Alley, Child in the Sky (Box 57)
        - Toyland [aka There Was Scarcely a Soul at the Thaw Trooper's Funeral] (Box 57)
      - Ispahani, Mahnaz (Box 57)
        - Mahnaz Ispahani to Q (Box 57)
      - Jacobs, Douglas (Box 57)
        - Boy with a Slingshot (Box 57)
      - Janowtiz, Phyllis (Box 57)
        - The Admirals at t he Poles (Box 57)
        - Birthday (Box 57)
        - Faculty Meeting (Box 57)
        - The Fire Eater (Box 57)
        - In the Nursery [aka queaky Nursery Tunes] (Box 57)
        - Madeleine (Box 57)
        - My Sister (Box 57)
        - Reunion with Jake at Still Creek Pond (Box 57)
        - Six Months After the Death of My Father (Box 57)
        - Stewardess to Passengers [aka Soon the Final Decree] (Box 57)
        - The Victims (Box 57)
        - Years Later (Box 57)
      - Jesperson, Ruth (Box 57)
        - Notes from the Underground Columns (Box 57)
      - Jiles, Paulette (Box 57)
        - Writings (Box 57)
          - Novus Magnificat (Box 57)
          - Collection of Works About Frank and Jessee James (Box 57)
            - The Irish Girl at the Pie Dog Hotel and Whorehouse (Box 57)
            - [This is a bank robbery…] (Box 57)
            - [September of 1876 Frank rides…] (Box 57)
            - Jesse Meets His Future Wife (Box 57)
            - Frank Retires (Box 57)
            - Frank Surrenders (Box 57)
            - Hiding Out in Tennessee (Box 57)
            - Frank Gets Nervouse About Jesse's Killer Instincts (Box 57)
            - Bandit's Wives (Box 57)
            - [Sitting around a slow, wet fire…] (Box 57)
        - Paulette Jiles to Q (Box 57)
        - Interviews (Box 57)
          - Roger Noon [aka Thomas Noon] (Box 57)
          - James Noon (Box 57)
          - Cissy Poole (Box 57)
          - Carolyn Poole (Box 57)
        - Blackwater, (2 folders) (Box 57)
        - The Late Great Human Road Show Galleys (Box 57)
        - A Manual of Ettiquette for Ladies Crossing Canada by Train Draft (Box 57)
        - A Manual of Ettiquette for Ladies Crossing Canda by Train Page Proofs (Box 57)
        - Excerpts from Northern Memoir Draft 1 (Box 57)
        - Excerpts from Northern Memoir Draft 2 (Box 57)
        - Wide Crossing, (2 folders) (Box 57)
        - [Untitled fragment] (Box 57)
      - Johnson, Curt (Box 57)
        - Skinning Cats (Box 57)
      - Johnson, Dennis (Box 57)
        - In a Public Place [aka The Heart] (Box 57)
        - The Landlord's Girlfriend (Box 57)
        - Where Have I Never Seen You Before (Box 57)
      - Johnson, Drew (Box 57)
        - An Embellishment (Box 57)
        - Rococo [aka Seventeenth Centruy Orange Juice] (Box 57)
      - Johnson, Gregory H. (Box 57)
        - Tactics of Angling (Box 57)
      - Johnson, Jonathan (Box 57)
        - Boiling (Box 57)
        - Mothere [aka Messages] (Box 57)
        - The One Last Thing [aka Remedial] (Box 57)
        - Open Roads (Box 57)
      - Johnson, Quendrith (Box 57)
        - The Great Supreme Being (Box 57)
        - The Suspended Visitor (Box 57)
        - The Letter Opener title page (Box 57)
      - Jones, James (Box 57)
        - The Merry Month of May (Box 57)
      - Jones, R. (Box 57)
        - Jumpers (Box 57)
      - Jones, Robert (Box 57)
        - Gordon Lish (Box 57)
        - Robert Jones to Q (Box 57)
      - Jurnovoy, Joyce (Box 57)
        - A Certain Smirk (Box 57)
      - Just, Ward (Box 57)
        - In His Time (Box 57)
    - Kamine - Kennedy (Box 58)
      - Kamine, Mark (Box 58)
        - The Return (Box 58)
      - Kaplan, James (Box 58)
        - In Miami, Last Winter [aka Harry Urbanie, Winning ] (Box 58)
        - How Bawble Made Them All Happy (Box 58)
        - Chicagoland (Box 58)
        - Permanent (Box 58)
        - Jerry [aka Bad Pets] (Box 58)
        - Reformation [aka Affirmative Action] (Box 58)